50statesclassifieds.com 2018-12-14

# USA Business Classifieds - Online newspaper classified ads Online Business Classifieds

|  |  [**Front  
Page**](http://www.50statesclassifieds.com/) |   |  [**Classifieds  
by Category**](http://www.50statesclassifieds.com/category.php) |   |  [**Featured  
Members **](http://www.50statesclassifieds.com/FeaturedMembers.php) |   |  [**Log  
In**](http://www.50statesclassifieds.com/signinform.php)  
---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
  
|   
---  
|  |  | **Featured**  
---  
  
 Attorney  

|   **Latest Ads**  
---  
| [ ESTATE SALE / Nov 30 & Dec 1 / 8:30am-1:00pm / Haverhill, MA ](http://www.50statesclassifieds.com/ad.php?id=199812)  
---  
[ ESTATE SALE / Nov 16 & Nov 17 / 8:30am-1:00pm / Haverhill, MA ](http://www.50statesclassifieds.com/ad.php?id=199801)  
[ Contents of House Sale / Nov 3 / 8:30am-1:00pm / North Andover, MA ](http://www.50statesclassifieds.com/ad.php?id=199797)  
[ Upcoming House Sale / Oct 26 & 27 / 8:30am-1:00pm / North Andover, MA ](http://www.50statesclassifieds.com/ad.php?id=199789)  
[ CASH PAID FOR YOUR DIABETIC TEST STRIPS Get Up To $35 a box ](http://www.50statesclassifieds.com/ad.php?id=199788)  
[ Michael Kors Women's MK3317 Slim Runway Analog Quartz Black Stainless Steel Watch ](http://www.50statesclassifieds.com/ad.php?id=199769)  
   
|  Privacy Policy for 50StatesClassifieds.com  
---  

#### SECTION 1 - WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?

  When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address.   When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computerâ€™s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.   Email marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send you emails about our store, new products and other updates.  

#### SECTION 2 - CONSENT

  How do you get my consent?   When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.   If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.   How do I withdraw my consent?   If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at webmaster@50statesclassifieds.com or mailing us at: 50 States Classifieds PO BOX 733, Menominee, MI, 49858, United States  

#### SECTION 3 - DISCLOSURE

  We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.  

#### SECTION 4 - WEB HOSTING

  Our store is hosted on Liquid Web Inc. They provide us with the web hosting and data transfer services which power our online e-commerce platform. This allows us to sell our products and services to you.   Your data is stored through Liquid Web's data storage, databases and the general web applications hosted there. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.  

#### Payment:

  We currently only accept PayPal and 2Checkout. Both of these secure 3rd party payment processors will process your transaction on their secure servers. Your payment information will not be stored on our website.   We do not currently offer any on-site direct payment gateway options to complete your purchase, but if we did, then 50 states Classifieds would store your credit card data. It would be encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.   All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover.   PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.   For more insight, you may also want to read the 2checkout.com and PayPal.com Terms of Service available on their websites.  

#### SECTION 5 - THIRD-PARTY SERVICES

  In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.   However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.   For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.   In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.   As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.   Once you leave our storeâ€™s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our websiteâ€™s Terms of Service.  

#### Links

  When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.  

#### SECTION 6 - SECURITY

  To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed. If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.  

#### COOKIES

  We allow Google and other 3rd parties to gather anonymous data from our users including, but not limited to:   browser and operating system information age and region other demographics   We have enabled all additional options in Google Analytics for gathering data and tracking eCommerce.   Please refer to the Google.com Privacy Policy for more information about the data they collect.  

#### SECTION 7 - AGE OF CONSENT

  By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.  

#### SECTION 8 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

  We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.   If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.  

#### QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION

  If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at webmaster@50statesclassifieds.com or by mail at 50 States Classifieds   [Re: Privacy Compliance Officer]   [PO BOX 733, Menominee, MI, 49858, United States]   \----   

---
